https://soec.org/privacy-policy/

Saleen Owners and Enthusiasts Club, LLCPRIVACY POLICY
————————-
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from soec.org (the “Site”).
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
– Communicate with you;
– Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
– When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@soec.org .
PRIVACY POLICY
TERMS OF SERVICE
CONTEST RULES
Recent Announcements
SALEEN 1 CUP CAR CHASSIS 15
November 9, 2020
VIDEO: REVIEW OF 88-0275 & 89-0639
October 26, 2020
April 1986
The Saleen ForumsSaleen wheel cap decals December 10, 2020Please share a source of the Saleen cap decal. Normally this would be the Saleen “S” with a gold or silver background depending on wheel and color of...SA 25 cams December 2, 2020Anybody happen to know what cams were used in the SA 25 ?Q: Windshield Banner Placement? November 30, 2020I've searched all the install bulletins and can't find the install bulletin for the decals on the S331. I just purchased new decals and the...06 S281E Twincharged November 25, 2020Hello, I have an 06 S281E with an exile twin turbo kit. I still have the Saleen supercharger. I have done a ton of mods to the car but most of...S331 Supercharged 2007 #007
Pre-Production November 20, 202042,000 Miles For Sale shimmersky@gmail.com https://photos.app.goo.gl/JHt1Uy6JwcpsB33f6
SOEC is the official independent, non-profit organization for owners and enthusiasts of vehicles by Steve Saleen and Saleen Automotive, Inc.
SOEC.ORG is proudly powered by WordPress
